FARZANEH HADADI TAHAROM

Front Web Developer

+98 912 467 63 71

Farzaneh.haddadi@gmail.com

🗣 Iran, Alborz, Karaj

Date Of Birth: February 6th, 1990, Iran

SUMMERY

Developer with 8+ years' experience working with different languages in web and windows Application, Proficient in JavaScript (ES6) and have experience with ReactJs, knowledge of design patterns, clean code and handling agile development methods (Scrum), A high level of responsibility and teamwork, have a strong interest in learning, Curious and motivated because programming is my passion.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Since 06/2019	SELF IMPLOYMENT
Ĭ	Working as a Front Web Developer with ReactJs, Javascript
	Completed online shop project based on React
	Design and establish user-friendly websites
06/2014-06/2019	MAPNA Electric & Control Engineering & Manufacturing (MECO)
Ţ	Software Developer in MAPCS Unit
	Developed and optimized programs using C#
12/2012-06/2014	Shabihbsazane Mantegh
Ĭ	
	Software Developer

EDUCATION

• BSc Information Technology (2010-2014) Shahrood University of Technology

TECH STACK

Windows Application	C#
	Visual C++ (MFC)
	C++
Front End Development	React js (React hooks, redux)
	Javascript
Style Sheet Languages	CSS
	SASS
	HTML 5
	BOOTSTRAP
Source/Version Control	Git/GitHub
	TFS
	SVN
	Visual SourceSafe

KNOWLEDGE AND INTERESTS

Foreign Languages	Persian (mother tongue)
	English (fluent)
	German (basic)
Hobbies	
	🛕 Yoga
	Cycling
	1 Chess